Well, no, no, no, I've never really thought about that.
I feel that the more money a person has, the more needs they create within themselves.
Even if they're things that everyone else sees as, let's say, stupid,
they're things that person keeps creating in their mind, simply because the more money you acquire, the more you feel the need for power, to have more.
So it's like a question of how much money you'd need to live the rest of your life.
Let's say, for example, that I need a billion pesos to live the rest of my life.
And you give it to me, a million dollars.
And you give me the million dollars.
alright, once I have it
I think I'll start thinking about buying a million-dollar mansion
and I'm going to need another million dollars
so I think it's a question that wouldn't have an answer
so I don't sit around thinking how much I'd need for my life
more than anything I need to be happy
to laugh and make a lot of music, a lot of music
that I do need, a lot of love
Hehehehe.